Guide to the Sam Adams Darcy Papers TAM.124
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VI. Biographical and other manuscripts., circa 1945-1971; 57253
  - Subseries E. Miscellaneous post-1945 notes, 57254
    - Book Four, Chapter One, The New Beginning, undated; 454750 (Box 4, Folder 7A)
- Series VII: Additional Correspondence, 57228
  Series 7 (Additional Correspondence) is principally correspondence with students, professors, and others researching the history of American communism and related topics. Principal and/or prominent correspondents include Jim Barrett (re William Z. Foster) and Harry Stein (re Lincoln Steffens).
  - Correspondence: A, 1961-1984; 57252 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: B, 1958-1982; 57251 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Barrett, Jim -- re William Z. Foster, 1986; 57250 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: C, 1958-1980; 57249 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: D, 1943-1948; 57248 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: E, 1954; 57247 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: F, 1934-1981; 57246 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: G, 1932-1984; 57245 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: H, 1970-1983; 57244 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence: I, 1977; 57243 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence: J, 1959; 57242 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence: K, 1951-1980; 57241 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence: L, 1954-1987; 57240 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence: M, 1954-1983; 57239 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence: N, 1956-1982; 57238 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence: O, 1967-1968; 57237 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence: P, 1942-1985; 57236 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence: R, 1935-1985; 57235 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence: S, 1948-1985; 57234 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence: Stein, Harry, 1966-1985; 57233 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence: U, 1979; 57232 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence: V, 1979; 57231 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence: W, 1940-1980; 57230 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence: X,Y,Z, 1925-1984; 57229 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Series VIII: Photographs and Graphics, 464790
  - 1928 Nomination Banquet of Communist Party, NYC, 464805 (Box OS001, Folder 4)
  - Acquaintances, portraits, events (Photographs and one negative), 1879-circa 1970s; 464799 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Burke, Jake; Daily Worker Cartoon (Furiers' Strike), undated; 479075 (Box MSOS004, Folder 2)
  - Burck, Jake: Daily Worker Cartoon (Gastonia Strike), 1929; 479072 (Box MSOS004, Folder 2)
  - Burke, Jake: Daily Worker Cartoon (Organizing Workers), undated; 479073 (Box MSOS004, Folder 2)
  - Burke, Jake: Daily Worker Cartoon (Peace), undated; 479074 (Box MSOS004, Folder 2)
  - Burial of J.H. Bland, Philadelphia, 1939; 464806 (Box OS001, Folder 4)
  - Burial of J.B. McNamara, undated; 464807 (Box OS001, Folder 4)
  - Graphics and Clippings (Strikes, Mother Jones, Frederick Douglass, etc.), undated; 464800 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Group involved in 1931 trial in Long Beach for conspiracy to commit criminal syndicalism, 464796 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Photographs of Newsprint Montages by Sam Darcy (includes San Francisco strikes, demonstrations, Mooney, Darcy trial), undated; 464808 (Box OS001, Folder 1-3)
  - Photo postcards (featuring prominent Russians and Marxists), undated; 464801 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Portraits, convention photos, circa 1940s; 464798 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Portrait of William Z. Foster, undated; 464804 (Box OS001, Folder 4)
  - Reference photocopies of exhibit boards, undated; 464802 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Series IX: Unprocessed Materials, circa 1930-1998; 1960-1985; 464791
  This series has not been arranged by an archivist. The materials are arranged in the order which they were received from the donor.
  Series 9 is comprised of materials that came to the repository after the initial donation was processed. Types of materials include manuscripts, articles, correspondence, and photographic and graphic materials. Much of the series is various drafts of the manuscript Tales of Three Worlds.
  - Unprocessed materials, 464816 (Box 4, Folder 38-47)
  - Unprocessed materials, 464844 (Box 5, Box 6, Box 7)
  - Unprocessed photographic and graphic materials, 553018 (Box 8)